What's up?
"What's up"?
You just left us. That's what's up.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Listen.
You're quitting the clinic, aren't you?
It's all good.
I'm gonna think about everything
carefully.
You should get some rest.
It'll be fine.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, good night.
Thank you very much, sir.
Thank you. Good night.
THE HAND OF GOD
Arata?
Mom.
Oh my goodness.
You're making another one already?
The competition is soon.
Sayuri!
Where'd you go?
You left everything out again.
Honey, if you don't stop,
Papa and Grandma will be mad at you again.
I have no desire
to stoke any conflict
or competition within my family.
So please, I'm asking you all,
let's not turn this
into some kind of family civil war.
This new venture of mine
shouldn't be making headlines.
But sir, this is news.
Aren't you essentially asking
for your daughter to step down?
No, I've never asked her to step back
from her duties as a doctor.
That said, I founded
the Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic,
and… and I gave it its name.
All I'm asking
is that she give the name back.
Excuse me.
In light of this request,
Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic
issued a statement
through its legal counsel,
stating that it has no plans whatsoever
to change its name.
The rift between father and daughter
seems unlikely to mend anytime soon.
Oh my God, you're leaving?
Did you find another clinic to take you?
I found a place that's hiring,
so I'll be interviewing there.
- What?
- Yeah, I'll send you the info.
Welcome back, Numata.
I gotta say, I don't get it.
Why would you come back to work
in the middle of this crisis?
Are you also going somewhere else?
Me?
- You won't tell anyone?
- I won't.
- Cross your heart?
- Yeah.
For sure. I'm on it.
I don't think you can keep a secret.
You're holding a press conference?
Director, we were advised to wait
by the legal department.
We'll lose staff if we wait any longer.
Won't we?
I'm afraid she's right.
I'd like it scheduled for today.
It doesn't matter where we hold it.
Director…
And before the conference,
I need to meet someone.
Get the car ready, please.
I'm sorry. I… I'm Dr. Tohyama,
and I was hoping to speak to you.
What do you want?
- I'd love to hear more.
- Don't get me started.
- You're all encouraging him.
- Come on, please.
As if I need it.
You wouldn't know it from looking,
but he's a huge mama's boy.
Come on, lay off it.
Talking like I'm still a child.
Aw, age has nothing to do with it.
A man doesn't grow out of his nature
just like that.
Though I admit, in your case,
you've taken loyalty to the extreme.
Mm! Oh, you think?
Oh, I know it.
You were heir to a construction empire.
But no, you didn't want any of it.
You wanted to carry on
your late mother's name and family line.
He has a point.
Goodness.
Didn't your father object
when you walked away from his name?
Oh yes, "object" is putting it lightly.
I was only a child.
But I didn't care.
You see,
there was no love lost between us.
It's funny how things work out.
Hmm? What do you mean?
Just that you turned your back
on your father,
and now your daughter Rin
is about to do the same thing.
Hmm…
You know? She's right.
It is funny.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's well said.
It is!
Stop!
Why are you doing that to Mom's birds?
I want you to forget about that woman.
Killed herself in the Odajima house.
I can't.
No! These birds were special to her.
She was a liar. Don't defend her.
Stop it! She wasn't a liar! She wasn't!
Her face was as fake as her background.
You know she had plastic surgery?
Thank you so much.
I appreciate you all being here today.
I called this press conference
to provide clarity.
To take responsibility and to be a leader.
I owe an explanation
to those who have supported the clinic
over the years.
So thank you.
I know this was on short notice.
Well, well, well, "Hand of God."
Let's see what you've got.
I have to imagine
what you're mostly interested in
are all of the rumors and speculations
flying around online
about my father and Tohyama Clinic.
But I will not be addressing that.
This press conference
is about something else.
Ms. Tohyama, what do you mean?
You don't have any comment at this time?
Interesting.
What I wanted to talk to you about
is how we'll be running things
from now on.
And also, the direction we intend to take.
The clinic's future is bright.
Fumi Numata.
That's a name
I imagine many of you recognize.
She was accused of medical malpractice
and criminal negligence
following the tragic death
of the model Kana Kokubun.
Nowhere to hide, Fumi.
However, the Tohyama Clinic and I
are very proud
to now be able to announce to you
that we have signed Dr. Numata
on to our team.
What?
There is more to Ms. Kokubun's story.
She was suffering
from early-onset breast cancer.
In order to treat her,
I advised her to have
her silicone breast implants removed.
She categorically refused.
Being a model, I can only imagine
how difficult the thought
of changing her body was for her
and how painful her decision was.
Our next step was to test the possibility
of seeing if we could find her
new replacement implants
and if they could be made more safe.
My team and I did our best,
but her condition degraded
quite quickly, unfortunately.
She was rushed to the Medical University,
where Dr. Numata chose to prioritize
saving Ms. Kokubun's life above all else.
She removed Ms. Kokubun's implants.
As a doctor, it's obvious
her decision was the right one.
I would've done the same.
What happened was a tragedy.
I do not blame Dr. Numata.
In fact,
some of the responsibility is mine.
It's time that I admit my fault.
I apologize
to Ms. Kokubun's family and fans.
On behalf of the clinic,
I'm so sorry for what happened.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive us.
Dr. Tohyama, can you tell us more?
Will Dr. Numata
be issuing another formal apology?
- So what are you going to do about Rin?
- What do you mean?
Listen, you know I've been
a big supporter of your business.
For a long time too. That won't change.
I'll do everything in my power
to help you.
However,
this very public spat with your daughter
isn't going over well.
And what's more, it's not a good look.
I agree.
You know, Rin used to come over
and play with Sara when she was little.
She's a family friend.
When Sara was diagnosed
with juvenile glaucoma,
Rin was always there for her.
She was so caring and attentive.
Why not let her use the family name?
Then you can bury the hatchet.
Dr. Numata is talented.
She's a very skilled surgeon.
Her philosophy
is in line with the clinic's.
She combines empathy with genius.
And by serving our patients
not just as clients but as human beings,
the Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic
will undoubtedly soar to new heights.
I truly believe that.
Seriously? What a joke.
So…
You wanted me to address the rumors?
I've said what I came here to say.
Hey, I'm home.
Fumi, do you want something to eat?
No, I'm good, but… what's going on?
You're just gonna ignore what Mom wanted?
What?
Mom didn't want you
to be a plastic surgeon anymore.
You can't just go back to work.
I thought it through. Don't worry.
Then tell me how.
How can you go back?
Standing in front of Mom's ashes
before going back to work.
Takeru's got a point.
If you're going back to work there,
you owe us an explanation.
Takeru gave you her savings so you could--
Now hang on.
Mom saved that money over 30 years,
and she never touched it.
What makes you think I can use it?
Huh?
You're just like her.
Stubborn as hell.
Takeru.
I know how Mom felt about it.
You don't have to lecture me.
I--
Don't walk away. Hey!
Takeru…
Screw this.
Cool.
So you're just gonna
drink your problems away.
Good idea.
Yeah. What else am I gonna do?
Explain my relationship to the chairman
to a teenager?
I don't think so.
But like…
couldn't you just leave the clinic?
Then it'd be fine.
I obviously can't. That's exactly
what the chairman would want.
Who the hell cares what he thinks?
'Cause you were, like, all gung ho
on taking Rin down, right?
It's just complicated.
Um, can I get another drink?
Sure thing.
Hey.
Why don't you do a DNA test?
No. What? Why would I do a test?
- You know I have evidence.
- What if he's not your dad?
Huh?
What if this "absolute worst" doctor
was somebody else?
Because then you'd have no reason
to help Rin, would you?
DIRECTOR RIN, RUI, HIKITA
NUMATA
TOHYAMA COSMETIC SURGERY CLINIC
DOCTOR NUMATA
Endoscopic surgery.
We're gonna start doing that here?
Yes, it's important for you
to have a signature procedure.
Doctors who have one
are much easier to promote.
We'll have it up and running by next week.
Next week?
The boss is bossy today.
The boss has a good head for business.
What was he like?
What was the chairman like as a father?
Huh?
I just…
I live with my stepdad.
So you don't have a biological father,
and… I don't have one either.
Oh, I understand.
I was
wondering what life was like
with your dad.
What was it like?
My parents had a hard time
conceiving a child.
That's why they adopted me.
Growing up, it was tough.
The other kids made fun of me.
Dad… he had a show on TV,
and he broadcast a photo of himself
pre-plastic surgery.
And it was so obvious.
We looked nothing alike.
I mean, of course,
I couldn't look like him.
I'm not really his.
Hey, Takeru.
Are you up yet?
I won't make you go to school
if you don't want.
But would you at least eat this?
I'm leaving the omurice here.
Make sure you eat it, okay?
I can't take it anymore.
He's still up there in his room.
Well, that does happen sometimes.
Yes, it does.
- Okay. Let's continue. Good.
- Right.
Next name?
It's…
Oh! It's Arata Tohyama!
Okay. Thick envelope!
- Ah! Yes! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
- Thank you!
Oh, Fumi's calling.
Yeah, Makihara here.
Oh, we were just getting ready
to write thank-you cards.
Hmm? The address?
I'm glad you came over.
Come in.
Hey, Sara.
What can I do for you?
Mm, I was thinking about, you know,
maybe getting
the new ultrasound treatment.
Oh, and I've been so tired lately.
I want an IV drip.
No problem.
Right this way.
How about I get you a drink?
Hang on.
Why were you there?
At my mother's wake?
Hmm?
Oh. Well, she was an acquaintance.
I knew her, is all.
You knew her?
You dated her once, right?
What is all this?
That's a strange thing to ask.
Dr. Tohyama, are you my father?
All right.
Let's say that I was.
What would you want from me?
- What would I want from you?
- Yes.
My daughter and I
are about to enter a legal battle
for the Tohyama name.
You're an employee of hers.
You might use any of this against me.
I don't care about your fight.
It's not like that.
That's not why I'm here.
I just….
Just what?
Uh…
My mother was in…
She went through a lot.
And I wanna know
what caused her to suffer like she did.
Grandfather's investing
in your dad's new clinic, apparently.
Oh. I see.
Better not lose. You know?
Huh?
I'd have to go to so much trouble
to find a new personal doctor if you did.
What Grandpa said to your dad at dinner
was that you should be able
to use your Tohyama name.
Now, what do you think
your dad said to him?
He'd rather be dead than let you!
It was so funny, Rin.
Why do you think it's funny?
None of this would be happening…
if you hadn't broken your promise.
What do you mean?
You told him about the accident,
didn't you? I know you did.
Here's what I propose.
You leave your job at Tohyama,
and I'll tell you what I know.
It doesn't make a difference where I work.
I have a right to know!
It may be your right,
but protecting the secret
your mother entrusted to me
is my responsibility.
This is a waste of time. Excuse me.
I'll see you there.
At my new clinic, that is.
What are you saying?
What I'm saying is that one day,
I'm hoping you take over as director.
Huh? That's never gonna happen! No way!
It was your fingers.
When I took your hand,
I just had a feeling.
Intuition.
I want you to be my successor.
What is so funny?
You think I said something to your dad
about you, don't you? But I didn't.
No, because if I told people what you did,
you'd be out of a job so fast
your head would spin.
But then I wouldn't be able to use you
as my own private doctor.
And that would be so dull, right?
You were at the hotel with him.
He invited me out to eat dinner, sure.
But we didn't talk about you.
You're gonna have to pay the price
for my eyes until the day you die.
My eyes! Why can't I see?
Director, may I have a word?
Sure.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
Did the chairman poach you?
Well, it can't stay a secret forever.
He offered me a job.
You never valued me here.
I thought you'd make
me director of the Ginza clinic,
but you didn't want to promote me.
You just wanted to use me
to draw in female clients.
I was a figurehead,
never getting the real prestige,
and being stuck with the boring surgeries.
I'm done.
Do you think the chairman
will treat you any different?
Well…
that's the thing about us.
We're all cut from the same cloth.
We cosmetic surgeons,
we work so hard in med school,
only to throw our integrity out the window
and chase money instead.
In the end,
I was presented with two offers,
and I made a choice.
Thanks for everything.
Excuse me, Director.
Hey, Numata, bad day?
Oh. You clocking out already?
She's just going to use you
in my place, you know.
Sorry?
I'll be waiting for you
at the new Tohyama Clinic.
Oh, you scared me.
What's wrong?
Me and my mom, we don't look alike, do we?
Oh. Well…
I mean, uh, we look alike, right?
I know it's because Mom had work done.
Huh?
I'M SORRY, ARATA
I LIED TO YOUR DAD,
YOUR GRANDMOTHER, AND YOU.
ODAJIMA CONSTRUCTION COMPANY
We're all set here. Hey, stay back.
Mom?
- Hey, Mom! Mom!
- Arata! No.
- Mom! Mom! Bring her back!
- Don't look!
- Stay here.
- Mom!
Mom! No!
Mom, wait!
I HOPE YOU WILL BE
A FINE HEIR TO THE ODAJIMA FAMILY.
SAYURI TOHYAMA
So, he didn't give you a straight answer.
Is he your dad or not?
Mm, maybe, maybe not.
Well, which is it?
Flip a coin!
You're messing with me…
Like, don't you need to know for sure,
one way or the other?
Yeah, that'd be nice.
But he didn't give me a straight answer,
did he? Whatever.
Maybe I should threaten him
with a knife, huh?
Another bottle?
Listen, Fumi.
Your brother wanted you to quit, right?
You can't go back to the way things were.
Ah! Excuse me! Another bottle?
Right away, ma'am.
I'm gonna go home.
Why?
Because I have better things to do
than sit across
from an irresponsible drunk.
I'm a what?
Things are tough for me right now!
- I'm just trying to survive here!
- Okay, fine. But let me ask you this.
If the chairman does turn out
to be your real dad,
what will you do?
You gonna keep it a secret from Rin
while you're working with her?
Because you could, but that's not right.
That's not what a decent person would do.
Let's go!
You never valued me here.
I thought you'd make me
director of the Ginza clinic,
but you didn't want to promote me.
You just wanted to use me
to draw in female clients.
Who's truly devious, then?
Don't pretend otherwise, Rin.
Why not give up the Tohyama name?
- What are you talking about?
- Mm.
It could be a fresh start.
What if you created a new name?
One that suited you better.
You could be free of him.
This public battle hurts you both,
and it doesn't do the clinic any good.
Tohyama is his mother's maiden name,
isn't it?
I doubt it means that much to you.
And I doubt he'll give it up.
Tohyama's my name, and I'll keep it.
Here's the thing.
My whole life I've wondered if I…
was truly worthy.
I may not be his actual daughter,
but they called me
the next Hand of God anyway.
I thought it was my destiny.
I've been fighting to be accepted.
To be worthy of the title.
If I run away now…
I'm afraid I won't be me anymore.
You know that's not true.
You've done great things.
- You're gonna keep doing them!
- It's okay.
I've got Dr. Numata.
And that means I can't lose.
Here you are.
Your patient list for the day.
Whoa, that's a lot.
It is, but you know about Dr. Rui?
Yeah, I get it.
Oh, there was a request
that came in from a patient
specifically for you, Doctor.
For me?
It's been a while.
I have to say I was surprised.
About Dr. Rin's press conference.
Yeah, me too.
I was pretty surprised myself, honestly.
Do you remember what you said last time?
That I should go back to my original face.
Yes.
That's what you told me to do.
I still think about it sometimes.
It was disrespectful.
I said some things I'm not proud of.
I'm sorry.
- But you've been successful regardless.
- I thank you for that.
How can I help you today, miss?
An endoscopic lift. I'd like to have one.
- You heard about that?
- I did.
Dr. Rin sent me a text.
You need a test subject.
She had great things to say about you.
Apparently, at the university hospital,
you were an endoscopic specialist.
That's a bit of an exaggeration.
Maybe so.
Dr. Rin's never tried to sell me
on any treatments before.
So I knew.
I knew I had to make an appointment.
Yeah.
Hey.
I thought you quit.
- Yeah, I probably should stop.
- Hey.
- Maybe today's the day.
- Hey, it's fine, it's fine.
You've already got the pack out.
What's one cigarette? Go on.
- I can have one.
- Mm. Go for it.
Yeah.
So you finally made your way out.
No longer on the dark side, are ya?
- What about you, Doctor? Huh?
- Not a chance in hell.
You know, it's funny.
Dr. Rui actually made me an offer.
"You wanna blow this popsicle stand?"
- You serious? What will you do?
- Uh-huh.
Too much trouble to quit now.
But then Dr. Rin got wind of it.
I told her the whole thing,
and she offered me a raise.
Nice. Nice.
Thank you.
And you,
you're just as stuck here as I am now.
Why's that?
Yeah. Endoscope's a big deal.
They invested millions in it,
and now that pressure's on you.
I'd hate that kinda thing.
I don't have time for it.
Three kids, plus my wife.
- You finding it kinda hot?
- Huh? Not at all.
'Cause I am feeling thirsty.
What?
You inviting me out for a drink?
SNACK BAR ITTENBARI
BACK IN BUSINESS
WE LOOK FORWARD TO SEEING YOU
- Yoko!
- Yoko, yeah!
Don't it make me cry
- Ooh!
- That's amazing!
Hey. Hey! What's going on?
- Water, please.
- What?
- I said water now.
- Yeah, sure.
Hey, what's wrong?
Takeru here, or what?
Is Takeru here?
Uh, he's, um…
- Upstairs?
- Probably, yeah.
Takeru.
Takeru!
Hey! Takeru! You in there?
I gotta talk to you.
Takeru! We gotta talk! Open the door!
Hey, hey, no! Stop being so loud!
- Bastard.
- You're drunk.
You wanted to talk!
- Just leave him alone.
- Hey, open up! Come on, hey!
Fumi, you're so drunk!
Huh? Who cares about that?
We have to talk. Now.
So open the door! Come on!
Maybe come back tomorrow.
Get off. Nobody asked you, Macky!
- That's enough.
- You're not part of this family.
So shut the hell up!
What did you expect would happen?
You've been ignoring him.
Nobody asked you. Now get the hell out.
You can't keep staying here!
Stop, please. Stop.
That what you want? I'll leave.
- Get the hell out!
- But you're being awful.
You're banging on his door, piss-drunk.
You're an asshole! You are!
You're being a shithead!
I don't need this from a freeloader!
That's enough, you two!
Back off and calm down!
Fumi, I get that you're going through
a lot right now,
but you're not the only one
who's grieving your mother's death.
I know I'm not your father,
and maybe it's not my place to say this,
but you're out of control.
Always coming home drunk,
lashing out at everyone.
Mommy was the same when things got bad.
I think it's time for you to leave, Fumi.
Fine.
I'll be going, then.
- We have just received word…
- Rin, come watch this.
- He won.
- …Ohkura has been projected to win.
What a comeback for Ohkura,
who many believed was at a disadvantage
after spending much of
the election campaign in a hospital bed.
A triumphant recovery
in more ways than one.
- Let's have a toast.
- Yeah.
Be right back.
Your opponent
has raised concerns about your stamina.
I think my illness provided me
with a unique perspective
that will be useful in serving you all.
Besides, my doctors have given me
a clean bill of health.
It almost feels as though
the rest and recovery
have made me ten years younger.
It's my goal to make Tokyo
a world-class beauty hub,
and I believe
the public shares my enthusiasm.
I want a future where people come
from all over the world to Tokyo
in search of youth and beauty
because we're the best there is.
So, the accountant handed me this today.
It's a donation request from an orphanage.
KOMADORI SEIAI INFANT HOME
- Is that from the orphanage?
- Yeah.
Guess it's that time of year again, huh?
- It is.
- Hmm.
You've been making donations every year?
This is the first I'm hearing about it.
Hmm.
They were good to me a long time ago.
I don't know.
Maybe it's been long enough.
Are you sure?
I mean, it is a wonderful cause.
Well, it's been a long time.
Over 30 years, in fact.
Whatever you want. I'll let them know.
DONATION APPLICATION FORM
DONATION AMOUNT: ¥1,000,000
- Hey.
- Hmm?
- It's time for the toast.
- Sorry, you're right.
Here.
- So, here's to you.
- Thank you.
LETTERS FROM FORMER RESIDENTS
KOMADORI SEIAI INFANT HOME
- She's beautiful.
- She really is.
I can't believe it.
She's a miracle.
The Tohyama name is hers now.
I guess that means
you're going to get busy again?
I am.
I've got some charcuterie.
- Oh, thank you.
- You want some?
If you don't mind waiting,
the doctor should be here soon.
Sure.
Hi.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Will you tell us
where you'd like the machine installed?
Mm…
It's your baby, after all.
You're going to do great things with it.
You okay?
Are you getting enough sleep?
Yeah. Anyway, over there.
Sure thing.
Uh, right up against the wall.
- Sorry about that.
- Are you sure you're not too tired?
I told you I'm fine.
Hang on. I'll handle this one.
- Huh?
- You can assist me this time.
Why? I'm fine.
You're not fine.
I could smell the alcohol
on you this morning.
You need to take better care of yourself.
I, um… I'm sorry.
Don't worry. It's over now.
I just need you
to be at the post-op review.
Director.
Uh…
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Nothing.
I'm really sorry.
Now, your recovery time begins.
Two weeks in your chrysalis.
It's very important to rest.
See, a butterfly needs recovery time
in its chrysalis
before it can transform
into something new.
Takeru.
It's completely normal to experience
growing pains during this period.
Change can be scary.
But just imagine how wonderful it will be
to spread your beautiful new wings
and fly towards the future you dream of.
We'll get through the tough part together.
We'll get you to the other side.
The new you is almost here.
In your case, Ms. Shimizu,
the swelling should be significantly…
- Doctor, there's a call from home for you.
- What?
The results will be worth it.
The previous procedure
is taking longer than expected.
We're very sorry.
We're expecting an update for you soon.
If you would wait here.
- Takeru, you need to hold still!
- Calm down!
- Let go!
- It's dangerous!
- I don't want your help!
- Don't move. Let me look!
- Calm down.
- Stay still!
I can't work if you fight me!
Damn it!
Why would you do this to yourself?
Like you'd even understand!
What?
Mom got plastic surgery, didn't she?
I just wanna look like her!
Come on, let me go.
Thanks, both of you.
- It's okay. I've got it.
- Okay.
Takeru.
I'm so sorry.
You're right, I didn't understand.
I was scared and lost.
I didn't know how to cope.
So I just avoided facing it at all.
I'm sorry, Takeru.
I'm sorry.
I'll never let you down again, okay?
I'm gonna tell you everything.
Would you please let me treat you?
Please?
What do you say?
Um…
Do you really want this surgery?
You tried to tell me before.
But I didn't listen, and I should have.
Look.
If this is something you really want,
then I'll do it for you.
It's your decision.
I want…
I want to change.
I wanna do it. I want to be someone new.
Even with plastic surgery,
you're still Takeru.
I know.
But I still wanna change.
Okay.
Leave it to me. I've got you.
It hurts, huh?
Do you mind
if I perform the procedure by myself?
It's fine.
Okay, let's get started.
Yeah, this part stings.
- Hang in there.
- Mm-hmm.
Hang in there. I've got you.
I know it's uncomfortable.
We're gonna get through this.
Okay, this is gonna sting a little.
There.
You won't feel the next one.
- No pain, right?
- Mm.
And now? Feeling any pressure?
- I'm okay.
- Yeah? You sure?
DEAR DR. RIN TOHYAMA
- Director.
- Ah, good morning. Is something wrong?
It's the endoscopic surgeries.
The bookings are really taking off.
FROM: FUMI NUMATA
SEND
Hey.
What? Are you still mad at me?
No. Of course not. I'm not mad at you.
- You're obviously mad.
- I'm not mad. I've never been mad.
You know what?
You used to threaten my whole family.
What I did was nothing.
Right?
Did you two talk?
You and Takeru?
Look.
Can't you tell what happened from my face?
Your face looks the same
as it always does.
Hey, can I get on this thing?
Sure, go ahead.
Okay.
It's nice.
I wanna drive to the sea.
- You mean today?
- Mm.
- I just want to.
- Huh? Why the sea though?
Can you take me there?
- Doesn't this thing go any faster?
- Yeah, it goes faster.
- You want faster? Hold on.
- Okay, I take it back. Wait!
Oh, Director. Governor Ohkura
contacted us earlier today.
He was hoping to come by for maintenance
and join you for dinner.
Ah, wonderful.
It's about time
the governor met Dr. Numata.
Would you let him know
I'll be bringing a guest?
Certainly, Director.
FUMI NUMATA
(NO SUBJECT)
To Ms. Rin Tohyama.
This may seem out of the blue,
and I apologize.
But there's something I have to tell you,
and it can't wait.
There it is! The sea! Check it out.
Fumi! Look, look, look, look, over there!
There it is!
I'm afraid I won't have the courage
to tell you in person.
So I'm writing to you instead.
The sea!
- Here we are!
- Hey, check out that bird!
- Where?
- Look, it's massive!
- What the heck is that? It's huge!
- I wouldn't get too close.
- Gosh! We're really here!
He hasn't admitted it yet,
but I know what I know.
Chairman Arata Tohyama…
…is my biological father.
I think it's time that I step away
from the world of cosmetic surgery.
MY LONG-LOST FATHER
No. No, no.
No! No! No, no! No!
No, no! No! No!
No!